Valentyna Tokarska

Front End Developer

I am a front-end developer with 2+ years of experience in JavaScript, HTML and CSS. My professional experience also includes working with React.js and Angular frameworks. I am committed to providing exceptional customer service and active participation in the work environment. I like finding effective solutions and ensuring a high degree of customer satisfaction.

Portfolio: https://tokkaya79.github.io/portfolio-tokarskaya/

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/valentina-tokarskava-708502252/

Github: https://github.com/tokkaya79

EXPERIENCE

CZ ImperialMedia

Location: Prague, Czech Republic Position: Front-end Developer (remote)

07/2021 - present Responsibilities:

- Web page styling according to the design/layout;
- Rewriting button logic;
- Introducing new components to existing projects;
- Refactoring written code;
- Bug fixes;
- Writing code that implements application logic;
- · contact with designer.

KIDS QUEST, Private Enterprise

Location: Mykolaiv, Ukraine Position: **Company Owner**

07/2016 - 02/2022

ENERGIA (Fitness Club)

Location: Mykolaiv, Ukraine Position: **Fitness Instructor**

05/2015 - 07/2018

BOROL LTD

Headquarters: Odessa, Ukraine Branch Location: Mykolaiv, Ukraine Position: **Chief Accountant**

02/2005 - 05/2015

TECHNO NIKOL, LTD

Headquarters: Odessa, Ukraine Branch Location: Mykolaiv, Ukraine Position: **Sales Office Manager**

08/2001 - 01/2005

COMPETENCE

- ability to work in a team and meet deadlines;
- basic knowledge of SEO for web application optimization;
- basic understanding of UX/UI design;
- solving issues related to cross-browser and cross-platform compatibility:
- strong organizational and time management skills in a dynamic environment;
- seeking and building long-lasting relationships with corporate clients.

CONTACTS

Wroclaw, Poland +48 730 699 868 tokkaya79@gmail.com

SKILLS

REACT Angular, JS(ES5,ES6) TypeScript PHP, MySQL, WordPress HTML5&CSS SASS, SCSS, Tailwind CSS GIT BEM

EDUCATION

European Financial University - Master of Finance 2000 - 2004

Commercial Technical School

- accounting and audit 1996 - 1998

LANGUAGES

- Polish B2
- English B2
- Ukrainian C3
- Russian C3

RECOMMENDATIONS

CZ ImperialMedia Mikuláše Kolník +420 777 529 017

HOBBY

- engaging in sports;
- social dancing;
- reading books in foreign languages.

ADDITIONAL

I hold a Category B driving license. (Driving experience for over 17 years.)